<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on For X Developers</title>
    <link>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on For X Developers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 20:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.tanaka.world/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The First Year of Engineering Manager</title>
      <link>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/the-first-year-of-engineering-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/the-first-year-of-engineering-manager/</guid>
      <description>3 years have passed since I joined Merpay. And starting Oct 2020, I&amp;rsquo;ve been an Engineering Manager (=EM). I&amp;rsquo;m often asked, &amp;ldquo;What does EM do?&amp;rdquo;, and I had thought it before I became an EM to be honest. I had feared of not writing code, but I figured out something against it. Will look back this year.
The definition of &amp;ldquo;EM&amp;rdquo; in the current company The definition of &amp;ldquo;EM&amp;rdquo; is different between company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Report - February 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/2021-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 21:40:53 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/2021-02/</guid>
      <description>English The second round of キク英文法 I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on the second round of キク英文法. For each grammar, I&amp;rsquo;ve made example sentences that I would use in my daily life and repeated it. Once a native speaker checked my sentences, it seems like &amp;ldquo;grammatically correct but not natural&amp;rdquo;. I would like to correct my nuance too.
Repeat 100 times I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying 英語は100回フレーズを練習して始めて自分の言葉となる for the past few days. It is not possible to be able to use a phrase when you hear at a moview or a book, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Report - January 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/2021-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 12:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/2021-01/</guid>
      <description>English Learning I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing development and 1on1 in English at my company, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been less trouble with English. My level is B2 Upper Intermediate of CRFR by some skill tests such as EF SET and a company&amp;rsquo;s english skill test including reading, listening and speaking.
I feel I have issues on Grammar and Collocation.
Grammar I&amp;rsquo;ve started studying fundamental grammar first to correct my grammar because I sometimes make mistakes in conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate package update and release with Cypress &#43; Renovate</title>
      <link>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/automated-pkg-update-release-cypress-with-renovate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/automated-pkg-update-release-cypress-with-renovate/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve automated the package update and release of https://tanaka.world/. When a npm package is updated, it will be merged and production deployed automatically after all CI jobs finish.
Example: The workflow for release
Renovate (Package Update) Renovate
Set up Renovate via GitHub App - Renovate. You can select a repo.
Cypress (E2E) Cypress
Previously, I tested manually when I updated. I&amp;rsquo;ve replaced the way to test with Cypress. It tests all pages roughly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrated From Hexo to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/migrate-from-hexo-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 21:35:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.tanaka.world/en/migrate-from-hexo-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve migrated the blog tool from Hexo to Hugo (The last moving: Moved from Middleman to Hexo)
Motivation  Hexo generator was really slow Dark mode support Multiple Languages support (To write in English too) Bored  I could have done 2 and 3 with Hexo, but I was looking for another tool for 4. To be honest, I didn&amp;rsquo;t think much about it and made a quick decision to use Hugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
